http://www.epowermark.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - E-Power Marketing® - Oshkosh, Wisconsin
Skip to content
1-920-303-1244600 Ohio Street Oshkosh, WI 54902
Request a Free Consultation
Facebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowLinkedin page opens in new windowPinterest page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new window
E-Power Marketing
What We DoOur Approach Inbound Marketing Content Marketing SEO Online Advertising Social Media Conversion Rate Optimization Analytics Local Search How We Bill
Who We ServeC-Suite Marketers Housewares Hospitality
Our StoryE-Power Team Client Experience Why Oshkosh? Join Our Team Success Stories Testimonials
Resources Blog Contact Us
Search:
What We DoOur Approach Inbound Marketing Content Marketing SEO Online Advertising Social Media Conversion Rate Optimization Analytics Local Search How We Bill
Who We ServeC-Suite Marketers Housewares Hospitality
Our StoryE-Power Team Client Experience Why Oshkosh? Join Our Team Success Stories Testimonials
Resources Blog Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which E-Power Marketing Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://epower.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by E-Power Marketing Inc.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
E-Power Marketing Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
You may learn how Google advertising handles your data at https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/
You may learn how to control Google ads from information at https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en
You may view a list of other third party service providers who collect information, and/or opt-out of such collection of information about you, by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
Changes to this privacy policy
E-Power Marketing Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
E-Power Marketing Inc.
https://epower.com/
111 N. Main Street Suite 405 Oshkosh, WI 54901
920.303.1244
consulting@epower.com
This document was last updated on May 8, 2018.
SUBSCRIBE TO OUR BLOG!
Search:
Recent Posts
How SEO Works for Local Businesses
A Look at Google Local Services Ads
7 Must-Try Ideas for Local Advertising
8 Tips to Get the Most Bang for Your Buck with Content
The Importance of Advertising on Facebook
Archives Archives
Select Month
Work at Home
READY TO TAKE THE NEXT STEP?Contact us today. We can't wait to hear from you!
600 Ohio Street
Oshkosh, WI 54902
Call us: 1-920-303-1244
Email: consulting@epower.com
Find us on:Facebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowLinkedin page opens in new windowPinterest page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new windowSUBSCRIBE TO THE E-POWER BLOG!
©2020 E-Power Marketing®. All rights reserved.
Sitemap | Privacy Policy | Terms
Go to Top
